{
  "question1": {
    "question": "What is Easons favorite game? ",
    "choices": [
      "Valorant",
      "School work",
      "Mobile legends",
      "Wait Eason plays games? "
    ],
    "answer": "Mobile legends"
  },
  "question2": {
    "question": "Who is Easons favorite youtuber?",
    "choices": [
      "Mr Beast",
      "Markiplier",
      "Jacksepticeye",
      "Manlybadass Hero"
    ],
    "answer": "Jacksepticeye"
  },
  "question3": {
    "question": "What is Easons favorite food? ",
    "choices": [
      "Fried Chicken",
      "Noodles",
      "Rice",
      "Sushi"
    ],
    "answer": "Sushi"
  },
  "question4": {
    "question": "Which teacher is Eason most afraid of? ",
    "choices": [
      "Mr Chennoth",
      "Mrs Liang",
      "Mr Irani",
      "Mrs Kaur"
    ],
    "answer": "Mr Irani"
  },
  "question5": {
    "question": "What is Easons favorite anime? ",
    "choices": [
      "Dr Stone",
      "Jjk",
      "Code Geass",
      "Fairy Tail"
    ],
    "answer": "Dr Stone"
  },
  "question6": {
    "question": "What is Easons favorite hero in mlbb? ",
    "choices": [
      "Ling",
      "Angela",
      "Clint",
      "Fanny"
    ],
    "answer": "Ling"
  },
  "question7": {
    "question": "What nationality is eason? ",
    "choices": [
      "Chinese",
      "Korean",
      "Japanese",
      "Vietnamese"
    ],
    "answer": "Chinese"
  },
  "question8": {
    "question": "What language is eason learning on duolingo?",
    "choices": [
      "Korean",
      "Japanese",
      "German",
      "What Is Duolingo?"
    ],
    "answer": "Korean"
  },
  "question9": {
    "question": "Which burgerking does eason work at? ",
    "choices": [
      "Manukau",
      "Botany",
      "Eason Works At Bk?!",
      "Pakuranga"
    ],
    "answer": "Botany"
  },
  "question10": {
    "question": "What does eason always say randomly?",
    "choices": [
      "Skidibi Toilet",
      "English Or Spanish",
      "I Love Calculus",
      "Aaaa"
    ],
    "answer": "Skidibi Toilet"
  },
  "question11": {
    "question": "Which council leader is eason in howick college",
    "choices": [
      "Bacot House Leader",
      "Hauora Council Leader",
      "Cultural Council Leader",
      "Academic Council Leader"
    ],
    "answer": "Academic Council Leader"
  },
  "question12": {
    "question": "How tall is eason?",
    "choices": [
      "160Cm",
      "170Cm",
      "163Cm",
      "165Cm"
    ],
    "answer": "165Cm"
  },
  "question13": {
    "question": "What makes eason sad?",
    "choices": [
      "Not Getting Excellence",
      "Saying Goodbye To Bed In The Morning",
      "Knowing He Got An Assessment Due Tomorrow",
      "All Of It Above"
    ],
    "answer": "All Of It Above"
  },
  "question14": {
    "question": "What makes eason the happiest? ",
    "choices": [
      "Petting A Cat On The Street",
      "Finding $20 On The Ground ",
      "Eating Delicious Food",
      "Getting Excellence"
    ],
    "answer": "Eating Delicious Food"
  },
  "question15": {
    "question": "Which of these is the truth? ",
    "choices": [
      "Eason Plays Piano",
      "Eason Is An Artist",
      "Eason Is Old",
      "Eason Is A Mad Scientist"
    ],
    "answer": "Eason Is An Artist"
  },
  "question16": {
    "question": "When did Eason come to howick college?",
    "choices": [
      "Year 10",
      "Year 9",
      "Year 11",
      "Year 12"
    ],
    "answer": "Year 10"
  },
  "question17": {
    "question": "What is Eason going to wear to uni? ",
    "choices": [
      "Shirt",
      "Hoodie ",
      "Jacket",
      "Suit"
    ],
    "answer": "Suit"
  },
  "question18": {
    "question": "What topic of calculus does Eason like the most? ",
    "choices": [
      "Differentiation",
      "Complex Numbers",
      "Integration",
      "Algebra"
    ],
    "answer": "Integration"
  },
  "question19": {
    "question": "What does Eason dislike in programming? ",
    "choices": [
      "Classes",
      "Tkinter",
      "Files",
      "Code Avenger"
    ],
    "answer": "Tkinter"
  },
  "question20": {
    "question": "Is Eason your favorite person?",
    "choices": [
      "Yes",
      "Meh",
      "No (O N O )",
      "He Is Cool"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  "question21": {
    "question": "What is Easons main language? ",
    "choices": [
      "Mandarin",
      "Cantonese",
      "English",
      "Korean"
    ],
    "answer": "Cantonese"
  },
  "question22": {
    "question": "Which uni is Eason going to?",
    "choices": [
      "Uni Of Canterbury",
      "Uni Of Otago",
      "Uni Of Auckland",
      "Aut"
    ],
    "answer": "Uni Of Auckland"
  },
  "question23": {
    "question": "What is Easons dream pet",
    "choices": [
      "Cat",
      "Dog",
      "Duck",
      "Bird"
    ],
    "answer": "Cat"
  },
  "question24": {
    "question": "What is the name of Easons family business? ",
    "choices": [
      "Howick Chinese Takeaway",
      "V8 Noodle Box",
      "Sams Lunch Bar",
      "The Bakery Shop"
    ],
    "answer": "V8 Noodle Box"
  },
  "question25": {
    "question": "What month is Easons birthday?",
    "choices": [
      "September",
      "June",
      "August",
      "December"
    ],
    "answer": "September"
  },
  "question26": {
    "question": "Which one of these is the lie?",
    "choices": [
      "Eason Has A Sister",
      "Eason Has Gotten Na",
      "Eason Has Never Gotten A Detention",
      "Eason Plays The Guitar"
    ],
    "answer": "Eason has never gotten a detention"
  },
  "question27": {
    "question": "Who is better in basketball",
    "choices": [
      "Andrae",
      "John",
      "Eason",
      "Denzel"
    ],
    "answer": "Andrae"
  },
  "question28": {
    "question": "What is easons favourite colour?",
    "choices": [
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Yellow",
      "Black"
    ],
    "answer": "Yellow"
  },
  "question29": {
    "question": "Which game is eason godly at timezone& \"c:/program files/python311/python.exe\" \"c:/users/eason/onedrive/desktop/internal programming/eason battle/adding_quiz.py\"",
    "choices": [
      "Wangan Midnight",
      "Ddr",
      "Fishing",
      "Taiko"
    ],
    "answer": "Ddr"
  },
  "question30": {
    "question": "Who does eason play in valorant?",
    "choices": [
      "Jett",
      "Phoenix",
      "Chamber",
      "Omen"
    ],
    "answer": "Chamber"
  }
}